《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously on AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
我們是能做成事的人
We are the ones who get things done.
我們能找到戰勝他們的方法
We can find a way to beat them.
塔拉  你在外面比我們走得都遠
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
至少你能告訴我們別去哪找
The least you can tell is where not to look.
好的
Yeah.
當然
Sure thing.
別這樣做
Don't do this.
我們要等待合適的時機
We need to wait for the right moment.
槍
Guns.
很多槍
A lot.
拿到后我們會加入你的戰斗
And then we fight your fight.
好的
Yes.
達成協議了
We have a deal.
謝謝你昨晚守夜
Thanks for keeping watch last night.
沒事  我喜歡
Oh, it's nothing. I like it.
今晚你來守吧
Uh, you can keep watch tonight.
我們今天會有收獲嗎
We gonna win today?
會的
Oh, yeah.
我們也需要給那個對講機找電池
We're gonna need batteries for that walkie, too.
讓它重新開始工作
Get it working again.
怎么了  笑什么
What is it? What's that smile?
我們出來幾天了  結果只找到
Couple of days out, all we got to show are
差不多兩把槍  幾個壓扁的豆子罐頭
two guns, dented cans of beans,
和幾件球衣
and some football jerseys, pretty much.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
我們在抗爭
We're fightin' the fight.
這樣更好
It's better.
早上好
Good morning.
如果我再聽見關于肥喬的一個字
And if I hear one more goddamn word about Fat Joey,
我就要打碎某人的牙齒
I'm gonna smash somebody's teeth in.
我看是甩掉了累贅
Good riddance to dead weight.
總算沒什么狗屁吉祥物了
No more mascot crap.
他們對椒鹽脆餅的品位不錯
They got good taste in pretzels.
還有電池
And batteries.
兩天了  我們得回去了
Two days. We're gonna need to get back.
瑞克
Rick...
再過一天半  今天和明天
Day and a half more -- today and tomorrow.
我們可以再出來  我們應該回去了
We can come out again. We should get back.
再轉會兒
Just a little more.
我們沒事
We're okay.
我們沒必要現在就找到武器
We don't have to find them right now.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
再轉轉吧
Just a little more, okay?
好
Okay.
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十二集』
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
我正想來拆線
Hey, I was just coming over to do that.
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻譯     冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
丹妮斯教過我
Denise showed me how.
我弄完了
I'm done.
翻譯     小酸奶 送小孩
怎么了
What?
沒什么
Nothing.
校對     送小孩
好吧
Okay.
時間軸     加森  濤濤
會解決的
It's gonna work out.
那是什么意思  塔拉
What -- What does that even mean, Tara?
后期     送小哥  拉圖
意思是我們現在有足夠的人手去戰斗了
It means we've got the numbers to fight now.
我們只用找一些槍
We just need to find some guns and --
你知道我們今天能在哪找到這么多槍嗎
Do you know where we could find that many guns today?
總監     送小孩
這周呢  今年呢
This week? This year?
你不知道
No. You don't.
我不能就這樣等著
I can't just wait.
我不知道你  但我不行
I don't know about you, but I can't.
我們會找到槍的  好嗎  我們會戰斗的
We're gonna find the guns, okay? And we're gonna fight.
這肯定不容易
Look, it's not gonna be easy.
不像上次哨站那樣
It wasn't the last time at the outpost.
也許你可以省點脾氣跟他們打
Hey, maybe you could just save all this for them.
給
Here.
能幫你的傷疤愈合
It'll help with your scar.
你留著吧
Keep it.
我們需要槍
We need guns.
我要去找
I'm gonna go find them.
該死
Damn it.
怎么了
What was it?
是一頭鹿
It was a deer.
我欠你一頭鹿
I owe you a deer.
之前那次
From before.
當時他們在門外
When they were outside the gate.
是啊
Oh, yeah, you do.
看見了嗎
You see that?
嗯
Yeah.
這種槍就是我們出來要找的
It's guns like that. That's why we're out here.
這里發生了慘劇
Something serious happened here.
很久以前
A long time ago.
是啊  這些子彈很不錯
Yeah. These are serious rounds.
也許這里也有好槍
Might be serious guns here, too.
我們上去瞧瞧
Let's get a better look.
好
Yeah.
該死
Damn it.
注意腳下
Watch your step.
也許我們不該在這里待太久
Maybe we shouldn't be up here too long.
我們去看看有什么吧
Well, let's see what we're gonna see.
士兵  平民  這些子彈
Soldiers, civilians, all those rounds --
曾有一場惡戰
There was a fight.
也許是行尸
Maybe it was the walkers.
也許是別的人
Maybe just other people.
他們還背著槍
They're still wearing their guns.
我覺得就是這里了
I think this is it.
我也這么想
I think it is, too.
覺得我們可以搞定嗎
Think we can?
可以的
Yeah, we can.
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
沒事  你呢
Y-Yeah. Are you?
我沒事
I am. ?
這是個預兆  對吧
This is -- This is a sign, right?
是的  肯定是
This is it. It has to be.
的確是
Oh-ho. It is.
即食口糧
它們是即食的
Well, they're ready.
我們吃吧
Let's eat.
我沒找到槍
I didn't find any guns.
如果你想知道的話
In case you were wondering.
我在外面找了一整天  一把都沒找到
I was out there all day and not a damn one.
一把真槍都沒找到
Not a real one.
問題是  我之前有一把槍
Thing is, I had a gun.
我本來打算用它殺了尼根
I was gonna use it to kill Negan.
我都已經準備好了
I was ready to.
假如我當時按計劃做了
And if I had done it, like I'd planned to,
如今尼根已經死了
Negan would be dead right now.
沒錯  也許我也會死  但誰他媽在乎
And, yeah, maybe I'd be dead, too, but who gives a damn?
那樣的話尤金就不會被抓走
Eugene would still be here.
奧利維亞會活著
Olivia would still be alive.
斯賓塞也會活著
Spencer would still be alive.
但如今他們都不在了  我卻還在
And now they're gone, and I'm here
就因為我愚蠢地聽信了你的話
because I was stupid enough to listen to you.
但你聽了
But you were.
也照做了
And you did.
你就站在那里對別人指手畫腳
You stand there telling people about their lives.
只對那些來這里的人
Only if they come here.
比如你
Like you.
就像現在
Right now.
你什么都不懂
You don't know shit about shit.
你說得對
You're right.
我的確不懂
I don't.
我說過你不應該去送死
I said that you weren't supposed to die
不應該去做那件你計劃要做的事
and that you shouldn't do the thing that you were planning to do
因為我們需要你
because we needed you --
我們如今依然需要
still do.
像我這樣的傻瓜都能看清那一點
Even a fool like me could see that.
死了的確更容易些
It's easier to be dead,
假如你還活著是我的錯的話
and if it's my fault you're alive,
那我只能背負著這個錯誤了
well, I'm just gonna have to live with that.
我當時決定要插手
I decided to meddle.
但我做的是我認為正確的事
But I did something I thought was right,
我也知道這事風險很大
and I knew the stakes were very high.
你當然可以因為自己還活著而指責我
You can certainly blame me for the fact that you have a life,
但之后呢  你要怎么辦
but after that what are you going to do with it?
你要如何促成那些必須發生的事
How are you going to make what needs to happen happen?
在你心跳停止之前  一切皆有可能
Anything is possible until your heart stops beating.
你能做的絕不僅僅是沖著個傻子大吼
Certainly more than yelling at a fool.
美國政府財產  嚴禁轉售獲利
即食口糧
7號菜單
牛腩配肉汁
火雞胸肉
什么
What?
如何
How is it?
棒極了
It's good.
所以  明天...
So, tomorrow...
我們出去  把武器搶回來  對嗎
we go out there, we get the weapons, right?
然后讓簡迪斯和她的人跟我們一起戰斗
We get Jadis and her people to fight with us.
我們殺死尼根
We kill Negan
以及其他該殺之人  來贏得戰斗
and anyone else we have to to win.
在那之后呢
And what happens after that?
之后  我們繼續生活
After that, we keep going.
是的  但是
Yeah, but...
尼根用他的方法統治世界
Negan ordered the world his way.
他死之后  我們應該建立新秩序  對吧
It's up to us to reorder it once he's gone, right?
所有社區
All the different communities,
可以一起想辦法  討論如何繼續生活
they can figure it out together, how to keep going together.
對  但總得有人促成這事
Yeah, but somebody's gonna have to make that happen.
總得有人負責  對嗎
Somebody will need to be in charge of that, right?
那個人應該是你
It should be you.
-不是我  -為什么
- Not me. - ?Why not?
你可以勝任的
You could do it.
你會做得很好
?You'd be good at it.
如果你想做的話
I mean, if it's something that you wanted.
我不想做  也不愿意做
Well, I don't think I do. Or I would.
但如果是咱們倆  你和我
But the two of us, you and me,
一起重建秩序
reordering things together...
那我愿意
I want that.
假如你也愿意的話...
If it's something you wanted....
我愿意
Yeah.
我要再吃五包這個  好嗎
I'm gonna eat five more of these dinners, okay?
知道嗎
You know...
我們用不著明天就搞定
we don't have to get it done tomorrow.
我們可以悠閑點
We can take our time.
過一兩天再走也沒關系
If we go another day, another one after that, it's fine.
我是說  這地方沒危險
I mean, the place is clear.
嚴嚴實實的
It's locked up tight.
只有一條路能進來  所以
We found the only way in, so...
我們應該回去
We should get back.
既然能拿到槍
If we're getting the guns,
多費點時間也沒關系
it doesn't matter if it takes a little longer.
等等  我一直
Wait. I've been, um...
在等著給你看這個
I've been waiting to show you this one.
這可是  辣椒  奶酪意面
It's, um, chili and mac and cheese...
大雜燴
together.
試試吧
Come on.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
我在思考
I was just thinking.
什么  你要這個
W..you...you want this?
恭喜
Congrats.
歸你了
It's yours.
是別人送我的  曾經幫助過我的某人
Someone gave it to me, someone who helped me.
她為我不顧一切
She put her ass on the line for me.
她救了我的命  知道嗎
She saved my life, you know?
她本來不用做  但卻做了
She didn't have to. But she did.
如今這是有意義的  毋庸置疑
That means something now -- it does. It has to.
要是我說了  知道嗎
If I say something, you know --
拿不到槍  瑞克是不會離開那里的
Rick won't leave there without their guns.
就算我們能成功接近那里
If -- if we could even get close enough,
她們也會開火  我們會反擊
they'll start firing, and we'll fire back.
她們應該跟我們并肩戰斗的
I mean, they should just fight with us.
救世軍殺了她們的父親
The Saviors killed their fathers
兒子和兄弟
and their sons and their brothers.
但她們不想和我們并肩戰斗
They won't want to fight with us.
她們只想藏起來
They just want to hide.
所以她們只能和我們戰斗
So they'll just fight us.
如果我告訴大家海邊旅館的事  就會這樣
I tell everyone about Oceanside, that's what happens.
憑什么我們的命比他們的更珍貴
What makes our life worth more than theirs?
就因為我們想阻止
Because we want to stop
那些傷害我們的人嗎
the people that are hurting us,
那些會傷害別人的人嗎
who will hurt other people?
該死
God damn it.
看
Look.
行尸在外游蕩  沒有被關起來
The walkers in the field, they're not closed in.
是啊
Yeah.
我們得干掉外面的這些
We got to take care of the ones out here
把缺口堵上  然后再慢慢干掉剩下的
and block that gap, too, so we can take the rest slow.
七  八...
Seven, eight...
九
nine...
我能用那輛車堵上
That car -- I can block it up.
我能干掉擋路的那一個
I can take out that one on the way.
你把剩下的引開
You draw the rest.
你給我留了八個
You're leaving me eight.
我們可以朝它們開槍
We could shoot them,
但這樣會引來其余的行尸
but that would call the rest from the field.
得悄悄行動  用劍
This is about doing it quiet, with the sword.
八個對你來說不是問題
You can handle eight.
你已經干掉八個行尸了  我推得動
You got your eight walkers. I can push.
我也行
So can I.
你只要負責把車開到缺口就行
You just worry about steering us in that gap.
該死
?Shit.
剎車壞了
The brakes don't work.
米瓊恩  你沒事吧
Michonne, you good?
沒事
Yeah.
你呢
You?
沒事
Yeah.
我覺得我們開過頭了
I think we overshot it.
你覺得還是你確定
You think or you know?
我確定
I know.
不過這是個好計劃
It was a good plan, though.
這個計劃超棒
It was a great plan.
就在這里吧
We'll do it here.
好
Yeah.
該死  這攔不住它們
Shit. It's not gonna hold.
過來了
There it goes!
我們散開  減少它們的數量
Split them off into smaller groups.
柵欄也許能擋住
The barriers might hold.
你去滑梯  我去摩天輪
You take slide, I take Ferris wheel?
或者我們可以直接逃
Or we could just go.
-你想逃嗎  -不  我們能搞定
- You want to go? ?- Nah. We can do this.
我知道我們能
Yeah, I know we can.
你那邊如何
How you doing?!
還剩八個
Eight more!
你呢
How about you?
十個
10!
瑞克
Rick!
米瓊恩
Michonne!
我試過了  但我還欠你一頭
I tried, but I still owe you one.
我可以在外面多待幾天
I could've gone a couple more days.
我喜歡那樣
I would've liked that.
我一直沒睡
I haven't been sleeping.
想著我們失去了什么
Thinking about what we lost.
想著我的朋友們
Thinking about my friends.
格倫救過我
Glenn saved me.
在最開始的時候
Right at the start.
而我沒能救他
I couldn't save him.
這很正常
It's normal.
我知道
I know that.
無法釋懷
Being stuck on it.
我們經歷了一些事
We went through something.
光這樣是不能釋懷的
This -- This doesn't cure it.
瑞克  我很抱歉
Rick, I'm sorry.
我們要反抗他們
We're gonna fight them.
這就是接下來會發生的事
That's what happens next.
我們會失去一些人
And we're gonna lose people,
也許是很多人  也許是對方
maybe a lot of them, maybe even each other.
即使那樣  也值得
Even then, it'll be worth it.
當我想到...
When I thought that...
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
你問過我
You asked me
放棄算怎么個活法
what kind of life we had just surrendering.
那不是生活
It wasn't -- It wasn't a life.
我們在那里做的事
What we did back there,
我們現在做的事
what we're doing now,
為朱迪思拼未來
making a future for Judith
為格倫和瑪姬的孩子拼未來
and for Glenn and Maggie's baby,
做出抗爭  這才叫生活
fighting the fight, that's living.
這是你讓我知道的
You showed me that.
你可以失去我
You can lose me.
-不  -你可以
- No. - ?Yes, you can.
我也可以失去你
I can lose you. ?
我們可以失去朋友  愛的人
We can lose our friends, people we love.
這不再是關乎我們了
It's not about us anymore.
是關乎未來
It's about a future.
如果我沒能活下來
And if it's me who doesn't make it,
你就必須帶領其他人前行
you're gonna have to lead the others forward
因為你有這能力
because you're the one who can.
但是
But...
你怎么知道
how do you know?
因為
Because...
你帶我走到了這里
you led me here.
全都能用嗎
Operational? All?
據我說知能
To the best of my knowledge, yeah.
可能需要清理一下  我們找到了物資
May need some cleaning. We found supplies.
要我們清理嗎
Expect us?
我們清理了一部分  上了油
We cleaned some. We oiled some.
剩下的你們來  我們是合作關系
You can do the rest. We do this together.
好的  但能用嗎
Yes, yes, but operational?
你可以開幾槍試試  如果你想的話
Well, you can fire a few. Try them out, if you like.
-多少把  -63把
- How many? - 63.
我們做了清單
We made an inventory.
不
No.
你是說不要清單嗎
You mean the inventory?
-不夠  -你說什么
- Not enough. ?What? - Wha-- ?What are you talking about?
你要很多槍  這就是很多槍
You asked for a lot of guns. That's what this is.
要為你戰斗  我們需要兩倍的槍
Enough to fight your fight. Us? Nearly twice.
需要兩倍的槍
Need nearly twice.
我們浪費夠多時間了
We've wasted enough time.
走吧  帶上槍
Let's go. Take our guns with us.
不行
No.
槍是我們的  協議還沒結束
Our guns to take. Our deal still on.
你們不能全拿
Not all of them.
我們留十把  為了找更多的槍
We're keeping 10 for ourselves -- to find more.
五把
Five.
-十把  -六把
10. ?6.
-十把  -九把
10. ?9.
而且要歸還貓
And the cat back.
二十把  貓歸我
20. I keep the cat.
我們給你找到槍  然后一起戰斗
We get you the guns. We fight together.
說同意
Say yes.
同意
Yes.
盡快拿來更多槍  我們就戰斗
More soon, we'll fight.
再多等幾天
You get a few more days
"接下來的事"就會發生
before "What happens next."
再多等幾天
Few more days?
沒錯
That's right.
我們會找到更多槍  想辦法解決
We'll find more, figure it out.
很快的
Soon.
再多等幾天
In a few more days.
你沒事吧
You all right?
沒事  我只是...正準備去找你
Yeah, yeah, I was just -- I was just coming over to see you.
怎么了
What's up?
你見到羅西塔了嗎
Have you seen Rosita?
今早換崗她不在
She didn't show for her guard shift this morning.
她大概出去找槍了吧
She probably just went out looking for more.
好吧
Mm. Yeah.
你為什么...
Why were you --
你為什么找我
Why were you coming by?
我要告訴你一些事
I have something to tell you.
你來這里是...
Are you here --
我來這里是找你幫忙的
I'm here because I need your help.
有一個條件
One condition --
要由我殺他
I get to take the shot.
好
Okay.
你帶橋上的炸藥了嗎
Did you bring any explosives from the bridge?
我考慮過
I thought about it.
但我不想被別人發現和阻止
But I didn't want anyone finding out and trying to stop me.
我帶了更好的東西
I got something better, though.
這樣你就能殺他了
So you can take your shot.
瑞克和米瓊恩找到了槍
Rick and Michonne found guns.
但他們沒準備好行動
But they aren't ready to move.
他們不能
They can't.
她們需要更多槍  更多人  更多時間
The need more guns, more people, more time,
更多借口
more excuses.
我記下了達里爾和卡爾給瑞克說的
I memorized everything Daryl and Carl told Rick
尼根基地內部情況
about the inside of Negan's place.
耶穌給我畫了一張外圍的地圖
Jesus made me a map of the outside.
非常遠  守衛森嚴
It's far away. It's well-defended.
-只有我們兩個人  -你要改主意嗎
There's only two of us. You changing your mind?
我準備好殺他了
I'm ready to kill him.
但我要確認你知道這意味著什么
But I need to make sure you know what this means.
你知道嗎
Do you?
他們不能活捉我們
They can't catch us alive.
如果被抓住  就給了他們借口
If they do, we give them something.
我們這是有去無回
It's a one-way ticket for both of us.
假如我們都去的話
If it is both of us.
我們都去
It is.